<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>For streamers on Peertube plugin livechat</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/eu/documentation/user/streamers/</link><description>Recent content in For streamers on Peertube plugin livechat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/eu/documentation/user/streamers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Some basics</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/eu/documentation/user/streamers/basics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/eu/documentation/user/streamers/basics/</guid><description>Enabling the chat for you live streams Instance administrators can choose to disable or enable chat in specific cases. Information in this section are only true in the default case.
When you create or modify a Peertube live, there is a &amp;ldquo;plugin settings&amp;rdquo; tab:
In the &amp;ldquo;plugin settings&amp;rdquo; tab, there is a &amp;ldquo;Erabili txata&amp;rdquo; checkbox. Just check or uncheck it to enable or disable the chat associated to your video.</description></item><item><title>Channel configuration</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/eu/documentation/user/streamers/channel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/eu/documentation/user/streamers/channel/</guid><description> This feature comes with the livechat plugin version 8.0.0, and can be disabled by your instance&amp;rsquo;s admins.
In the Peertube left menu, there is a &amp;ldquo;Chatrooms&amp;rdquo; entry:
This &amp;ldquo;Chatrooms&amp;rdquo; link takes you to a list of your channels. By clicking on a channel, you will then be able to setup some options for your channels:
Here you can configure:
The slow mode The chat bot More features to come&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Slow mode</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/eu/documentation/user/streamers/slow_mode/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/eu/documentation/user/streamers/slow_mode/</guid><description>This feature comes with the livechat plugin version 8.3.0.
Introduction As a streamer, you can choose to rate limit your viewers messages in the chat.
This can be really usefull to:
avoid message flooding avoid unreadable chat if there are many viewers talking You can set a number of seconds that users will have to wait after sending a message, before sending another.
This limitation does not apply to moderators.</description></item><item><title>Tasks / TODO-list</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/eu/documentation/user/streamers/tasks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/eu/documentation/user/streamers/tasks/</guid><description>This feature comes with the livechat plugin version 10.0.0.
Introduction The livechat plugin includes a Task Application: a kind of &amp;ldquo;TODO-list&amp;rdquo; features where you can create task lists and add tasks to them. All room&amp;rsquo;s admins have access to these tasks, so you can edit them collaboratively.
You can for example use the Task Application to:
prepare a list of themes you want to discuss during your live stream, so you can be sure you won&amp;rsquo;t forget anything note down questions from your viewers, so you can come back to them later without forgetting to answer them &amp;hellip; Using the Task Application Opening the Task Application To open the Task Application, there is a &amp;ldquo;Tasks&amp;rdquo; button in the chat top menu:</description></item><item><title>Moderation</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/eu/documentation/user/streamers/moderation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/eu/documentation/user/streamers/moderation/</guid><description>This section is still incomplete.
The chat bot You can use a chat bot, that will help you for moderation. Check the chat bot documentation for more information.
Accessing moderation tools You can access room settings and moderation tools using the chat dropdown menu at the top of the chat.
All instance moderators and admins will be owner of created chat rooms. The video owner will be admin in the chat room.</description></item></channel></rss>