<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Peertube plugin livechat documentation</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/</link><description>Recent content on Peertube plugin livechat documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Known issues: CPU Compatibility</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/documentation/installation/cpu_compatibility/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/documentation/installation/cpu_compatibility/</guid><description>The Prosody AppImage included in the plugin will only work on x86_64 CPU. It is not compatible with arm64 and other CPU architectures.
For now, I did not manage to make it work for other CPU architectures. If you want te be notified when it will be possible, you can subscribe and comment this issue.
To use the plugin, you will have to manually install Prosody on your server (see below).</description></item><item><title>Moderation</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/documentation/user/moderation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/documentation/user/moderation/</guid><description>You can access room settings and moderation tools by opening the chat in a new window, and using the dropdown menu at the top right.
You can list all existing chatrooms: in the plugin settings screen, there is a button «List rooms».
You can delete old rooms: join the room, and use the menu on the top to destroy the room.
Notes All instance moderators and admins will be owner of created chat rooms.</description></item><item><title>OBS</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/documentation/user/obs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/documentation/user/obs/</guid><description>OBS Overlay If you are using OBS for streaming, you can easily include the chat in your stream.
You can use the «share chat link» feature to generate an URL to your chat. The button should be near the chat if you are the video owner (unless it was desactivated by your server admins).
Check the «readonly» checkbox in the modal. Then use this link as a «web browser source» in OBS.</description></item><item><title>Settings</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/documentation/admin/settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/documentation/admin/settings/</guid><description>This section describes the plugin settings page.
List existing rooms When pressing the «List rooms» button, all existing chatrooms will be listed. You can then find them and moderated them.
Chat behaviour Room type You can choose here to have separate rooms for each video, or to group them by channel.
Automatically open the chat If checked, the chat will be loaded as soon as you are on the video page.</description></item><item><title>Upgrade from version older than 6.0.0</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/documentation/installation/upgrade_before_6.0.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/documentation/installation/upgrade_before_6.0.0/</guid><description>IMPORTANT NOTE Since version v6.0.0, this plugin does not need any Prosody installation.
If you were using this plugin before this version, and if you had installed Prosody manually, you can safely uninstall Prosody.
If you were using the custom Peertube docker image that is embedding Prosody, you can switch back to the official Peertube image.</description></item><item><title>Using Matterbridge</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/documentation/admin/advanced/matterbridge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/documentation/admin/advanced/matterbridge/</guid><description>Here is a tutorial to use Matterbridge with the plugin: https://gitlab.com/refrac/obs-matterbridge-overlay/-/blob/master/documentation/peertube.md</description></item></channel></rss>