<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Peertube plugin livechat</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/</link><description>Recent content on Peertube plugin livechat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>For viewers</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/viewers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/viewers/</guid><description>Joining chat rooms When you are watching a Peertube video that has the chat activated, you will see the chat next to the video:
Postoje dva različita slučaja upotrebe, ovisno o tome imaš li račun na Peertube instanci ili ne. Pogledaj dolje za više informacija.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t a Peertube account This feature can be disabled by the instance&amp;rsquo;s adminitrators.
If you are not logged in on the Peertube instance where you are watching the video, you will automatically join the chat.</description></item><item><title>Forbidden words</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/streamers/bot/forbidden_words/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/streamers/bot/forbidden_words/</guid><description>Možeš konfigurirati neke riječi koje će bot automatski moderirati (poruke koje sadrže takve riječi će se odmah izbrisati). Možeš dodati i opcionalni razlog koji će se prikazati na mjestu izbrisanih poruka. Stranica dokumentacije sadrži nekoliko primjera. You can fill several &amp;ldquo;Zabranjene riječi i izrazi&amp;rdquo; fields. When a user sends a message that match the configured criteria, the message will automatically be deleted.
Zabranjene riječi i izrazi In this field, you can set several words, group of words, or &amp;ldquo;regular expressions&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Postavke</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/admin/settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/admin/settings/</guid><description>This section describes the plugin settings page.
Prikaži popis postojećih soba When pressing the «List rooms» button, all existing chatrooms will be listed. You can then find them and moderated them.
Federacija Following settings concern the federation with other Peertube instances, and other fediverse softwares.
Don't display remote chats By checking this setting, your instance will never display chats from remote videos. Nemoj objaviti podatke chata By checking this setting, your instance will not publish chat information on the fediverse.</description></item><item><title>Some basics</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/streamers/basics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/streamers/basics/</guid><description>Enabling the chat for you live streams Instance administrators can choose to disable or enable chat in specific cases. Information in this section are only true in the default case.
When you create or modify a Peertube live, there is a &amp;ldquo;plugin settings&amp;rdquo; tab:
In the &amp;ldquo;plugin settings&amp;rdquo; tab, there is a &amp;ldquo;Koristi chat&amp;rdquo; checkbox. Just check or uncheck it to enable or disable the chat associated to your video.</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/installation/troubleshooting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/installation/troubleshooting/</guid><description>I just installed/upgraded the plugin, but nothing happens If you have just installed/upgraded the plugin, but nothing happens (no chat, no settings, buttons in the settings page does not work, &amp;hellip;), just try to reload the page.
Diagnostic tool If the chat does not work, there is a diagnostic tool in the plugin&amp;rsquo;s settings pages.
Open the plugin settings, and click on the &amp;ldquo;launch diagnostic&amp;rdquo; button.
If there is any error in the diagnostic page, you can search in this page for a solution, or refer to the Bug tracking documentation page if you can&amp;rsquo;t find any response.</description></item><item><title>External Authentication</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/admin/external_auth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/admin/external_auth/</guid><description>Users that are not connected to your Peertube instance are joining the chat using &amp;ldquo;anonymous accounts&amp;rdquo; (they can freely choose a nickname, and will be assigned a random avatar).
You can enable some external authentication methods to allow user to create chat accounts. In such case their nickname and avatar will be automatically initialized with the remote account information.
Such &amp;ldquo;external account users&amp;rdquo; will be easier to moderate than anonymous accounts.</description></item><item><title>Known issues: CPU Compatibility</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/installation/cpu_compatibility/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/installation/cpu_compatibility/</guid><description>The Prosody AppImage included in the plugin will only work on x86_64 and arm64 CPU. It is not compatible with other CPU architectures.
To use the plugin, you will have to manually install Prosody on your server (see below).
Napomena: dodatak zahtijeva Prosody verziju ≥ 0.12.0. Ako koristiš stariju verziju, Chat Federation možda neće raditi i može doći do neočekivanog ponašanja.
Once it is done, you have to check Use system Prosody in the plugin settings.</description></item><item><title>Timers</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/streamers/bot/quotes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/streamers/bot/quotes/</guid><description>Možeš konfigurirati nekoliko timera koji će slati poruke u intervalima. Ove će poruke bot slati svakih X minuta. Na primjer, možeš postaviti bota da šalje neke informacije o sponzoriranju svakih 5 minuta. If there is no user in the chatroom, the bot won&amp;rsquo;t send any message.
Timer Možeš konfigurirati nekoliko timera koji će slati poruke u intervalima. Ove će poruke bot slati svakih X minuta. Na primjer, možeš postaviti bota da šalje neke informacije o sponzoriranju svakih 5 minuta.</description></item><item><title>Channel configuration</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/streamers/channel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/streamers/channel/</guid><description> This feature comes with the livechat plugin version 8.0.0, and can be disabled by your instance&amp;rsquo;s admins.
In the Peertube left menu, there is a &amp;ldquo;Chat sobe&amp;rdquo; entry:
This &amp;ldquo;Chat sobe&amp;rdquo; link takes you to a list of your channels. By clicking on a channel, you will then be able to setup some options for your channels:
Here you can configure:
The slow mode The chat bot More features to come&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Slow mode</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/streamers/slow_mode/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/streamers/slow_mode/</guid><description>This feature comes with the livechat plugin version 8.3.0.
Introduction As a streamer, you can choose to rate limit your viewers messages in the chat.
This can be really usefull to:
avoid message flooding avoid unreadable chat if there are many viewers talking You can set a number of seconds that users will have to wait after sending a message, before sending another.
This limitation does not apply to moderators.</description></item><item><title>XMPP clients</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/admin/advanced/xmpp_clients/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/admin/advanced/xmpp_clients/</guid><description>This chat module is based on the XMPP protocol, also known as Jabber. It is therefore possible to connect to the chats using XMPP client software. This can for example be useful to facilitate moderation operations.
For the user documentation associated with these features, please refer to the user documentation page.
Enabling these features requires configuration changes on the server, and on the DNS records. It is not possible to configure this only from the Peertube interface, and it requires some basic system some basic system admin skills.</description></item><item><title>Tasks / TODO-list</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/streamers/tasks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/streamers/tasks/</guid><description>This feature comes with the livechat plugin version 10.0.0.
Introduction The livechat plugin includes a Task Application: a kind of &amp;ldquo;TODO-list&amp;rdquo; features where you can create task lists and add tasks to them. All room&amp;rsquo;s admins have access to these tasks, so you can edit them collaboratively.
You can for example use the Task Application to:
prepare a list of themes you want to discuss during your live stream, so you can be sure you won&amp;rsquo;t forget anything note down questions from your viewers, so you can come back to them later without forgetting to answer them &amp;hellip; Using the Task Application Opening the Task Application To open the Task Application, there is a &amp;ldquo;Tasks&amp;rdquo; button in the chat top menu:</description></item><item><title>Commands</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/streamers/bot/commands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/streamers/bot/commands/</guid><description>Možeš konfigurirati bota da odgovara na naredbe. Naredba je poruka koja počinje s uskličnikom (!). Na primjer „!help” poziva naredbu „help”. You can setup several commands.
Naredba Naredba, bez uskličnika na početku. Na primjer „pomoć”, „sponzor”, … Šalji svakih X minuta Bot će slati poruku svakih X minuta.</description></item><item><title>OBS</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/obs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/obs/</guid><description>OBS is a popular Free And Open Source streaming software, with advanced capacities for your live streams. In the current page, you will find some advices to handle your live chats using OBS.
OBS Overlay You can easily include the chat in your stream.
You can use the &amp;ldquo;Dijeli poveznicu chata&amp;rdquo; feature to generate an URL to your chat. This button should be near the chat if you are the video owner (unless it was desactivated by your server admins).</description></item><item><title>Upgrade from version older than 6.0.0</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/installation/upgrade_before_6.0.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/installation/upgrade_before_6.0.0/</guid><description>IMPORTANT NOTE Since version v6.0.0, this plugin does not need any Prosody installation.
If you were using this plugin before this version, and if you had installed Prosody manually, you can safely uninstall Prosody.
If you were using the custom Peertube docker image that is embedding Prosody, you can switch back to the official Peertube image.</description></item><item><title>Using Matterbridge</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/admin/advanced/matterbridge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/admin/advanced/matterbridge/</guid><description>Here is a tutorial to use Matterbridge with the plugin: https://gitlab.com/refrac/obs-matterbridge-overlay/-/blob/master/documentation/peertube.md</description></item><item><title>Moderation</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/streamers/moderation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/streamers/moderation/</guid><description>This section is still incomplete.
The chat bot You can use a chat bot, that will help you for moderation. Check the chat bot documentation for more information.
Accessing moderation tools You can access room settings and moderation tools using the chat dropdown menu at the top of the chat.
All instance moderators and admins will be owner of created chat rooms. The video owner will be admin in the chat room.</description></item><item><title>MUC Slow mode</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/technical/slow_mode/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/technical/slow_mode/</guid><description>The livechat plugin includes a &amp;ldquo;slow mode&amp;rdquo; feature, to rate limit the number of messages that a user can send to a given MUC room. At time of writing, there were no XEP to describe such feature. Please find below a XEP draft, that will be submitted for review.
Work In Progress, this page is not done yet. For an updated version of this document, you can check the draft XEP XMP file.</description></item><item><title>XMPP Clients</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/xmpp_clients/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/hr/documentation/user/xmpp_clients/</guid><description>This chat plugin relies on the XMPP protocol (also known as Jabber). It is therefore possible to connect to the chats using XMPP client software. This can be useful for example to facilitate moderation operations.
The features described on this page must be enabled and configured by your Peertube instance&amp;rsquo;s administrators. You may therefore not have access to them.
Login to your Peertube account This feature is not yet available, and will come in a future version of the plugin.</description></item></channel></rss>