<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>User documentation on Peertube plugin livechat</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/sv/documentation/user/</link><description>Recent content in User documentation on Peertube plugin livechat</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/sv/documentation/user/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>For viewers</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/sv/documentation/user/viewers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/sv/documentation/user/viewers/</guid><description>Joining chat rooms When you are watching a Peertube video that has the chat activated, you will see the chat next to the video:
There are two slightly different use cases, depending on wether or not you have an account on the Peertube instance. See bellow for more informations.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t a Peertube account This feature can be disabled by the instance&amp;rsquo;s adminitrators.
If you are not logged in on the Peertube instance where you are watching the video, you will automatically join the chat.</description></item><item><title>For streamers</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/sv/documentation/user/streamers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/sv/documentation/user/streamers/</guid><description>Enabling the chat for you live streams Instance administrators can choose to disable or enable chat in specific cases. Information in this section are only true in the default case.
When you create or modify a Peertube live, there is a &amp;ldquo;plugin settings&amp;rdquo; tab:
In the &amp;ldquo;plugin settings&amp;rdquo; tab, there is a &amp;ldquo;Use chat&amp;rdquo; checkbox. Just check or uncheck it to enable or disable the chat associated to your video.</description></item><item><title>Moderation</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/sv/documentation/user/moderation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/sv/documentation/user/moderation/</guid><description>This section is still incomplete.
Accessing moderation tools You can access room settings and moderation tools by opening the chat in a new window, and using the dropdown menu at the top right.
All instance moderators and admins will be owner of created chat rooms. The video owner will be admin in the chat room.
You can use ConverseJS moderation commands to moderate the room. When you open the chat room in full screen, there will also be a menu with dedicated commands on the top right.</description></item><item><title>OBS</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/sv/documentation/user/obs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/sv/documentation/user/obs/</guid><description>OBS is a popular Free And Open Source streaming software, with advanced capacities for your live streams. In the current page, you will find some adviced to handle your live chats using OBS.
OBS Overlay You can easily include the chat in your stream.
You can use the &amp;ldquo;Share chat link&amp;rdquo; feature to generate an URL to your chat. This button should be near the chat if you are the video owner (unless it was desactivated by your server admins).</description></item><item><title>XMPP Clients</title><link>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/sv/documentation/user/xmpp_clients/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://johnxlivingston.github.io/peertube-plugin-livechat/sv/documentation/user/xmpp_clients/</guid><description>This chat plugin relies on the XMPP protocol (also known as Jabber). It is therefore possible to connect to the chats using XMPP client software. This can be useful for example to facilitate moderation operations.
The features described on this page must be enabled and configured by your Peertube instance&amp;rsquo;s administrators. You may therefore not have access to them.
Login to your Peertube account This feature is not yet available, and will come in a future version of the plugin.</description></item></channel></rss>